http://www.sundaycross.com/privacy-policy

My Account
Register
Login
Wish List (0)
Shopping Cart
Checkout
Categories
cross necklace
big cross necklace (22)
celtic cross necklace (30)
contemporary cross necklace (130)
cross necklace for her (332)
cross necklace for him (229)
crucifix cross necklace (43)
designer cross necklace (327)
golden cross necklace (19)
gothic cross necklace (100)
onyx cross necklace (19)
pewter cross necklace (21)
picture frame cross necklace (5)
rhinestone cross necklace (134)
shell cross necklace (4)
silver toned cross necklace (161)
stainless steel cross necklace (122)
titanium cross necklace (26)
victorian cross necklace (83)
wood cross necklace (28)
See All cross necklace
cross pendant
crucifix cross pendant (4)
stainless steel cross pendant (54)
titanium cross pendant (2)
See All cross pendant
cross bracelet
celtic cross bracelet (1)
cross bracelet for her (28)
cross bracelet for him (23)
designer cross bracelet (21)
gothic cross bracelet (3)
pewter cross bracelet (2)
silver toned cross bracelet (3)
stainless steel cross bracelet (3)
victorian cross bracelet (5)
See All cross bracelet
cross ring
cross by design
big cross necklace (22)
celtic cross necklace (31)
contemporary cross necklace (141)
cross necklace for her (360)
cross necklace for him (252)
crucifix cross necklace (10)
designer cross necklace (349)
gothic cross necklace (103)
victorian cross necklace (88)
See All cross by design
cross by material
golden cross necklace (19)
onyx cross necklace (19)
pewter cross bracelet (2)
pewter cross necklace (21)
rhinestone cross necklace (131)
shell cross necklace (4)
silver toned cross necklace (164)
stainless steel cross necklace (193)
titanium cross necklace (28)
wood cross necklace (28)
See All cross by material
chain
crucifix cross necklace
charms
heart jewelry (27)
keychain cross (3)
special christmas (14)
See All charms
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
At sundaycross.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. sundaycross.com does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. We use the information we collect about you to process orders only. When you Place your order, we request your credit card billing information for order processing, order fulfillment, and order tracking. We may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes at sundaycross.com and special offers we think you will find valuable.By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your contact information by sundaycross.com for order transaction purposes only. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.Every time you shop with sundaycross.com, you are backed by not only our security guarantee, but also that of PayPal's security guarantee. sundaycross.com utilize PayPal to process your orders. This encryption ensures that no one can access or use your personal information.Secured Order Processing is provided by . PayPal is an eBay company.Please click [here] for detailed explaination of PayPal's security.We are confident that your information cannot be compromised as a result of shopping at sundaycross.com. If you think your credit card has been compromised as a result of shopping at sundaycross.com, please contact your credit card provider immediately.Questions about this policy may be addressed to info@sundaycross.com.
